Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Project Files, 1965-1995; Series IX
  - Len Barson, 1975-1986; Subseries 1
    - Nuclear Waste: Low Level Waste Compacts, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 398/11)
    - Nuclear Waste: Low Level Waste Compacts - Senate, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 398/12)
    - Nuclear Waste: Low Level Waste Compacts - Senate, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 398/13)
    - Nuclear Waste: Low Level Waste Hearing, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/1)
    - Nuclear Waste: Low Level Waste Hearing, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/2)
    - Nuclear Waste: Low Level Waste Press, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/3)
    - Nuclear Waste: Nuclear Regulatory Commission Authorization, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/4)
    - Nuclear Waste: Plutonium Nonproliferation, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/5)
    - Nuclear Waste: Reactor Decommissioning, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/6)
    - Nuclear Waste: "Source Term" Research, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/7)
    - Nuclear Waste: Submarine Proposal, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/8)
    - Nuclear Waste: Westinghouse Space Reactor, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 399/9)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: Asia Trade, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 399/10)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: China, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 399/11)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: China, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/1)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: China, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/2)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: China Hearing, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/3)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: China Task Force, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/4)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: China Timber, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/5)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: Japan and Korea Trade, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/6)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: Pacific Committee, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/7)
    - Pacific Rim Trade: Subcommittee on Trade with China, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/8)
    - Roos, John: Pacific Salmon Fisheries Commission Director, 1986 (Box-folder 400/9)
    - Steelhead Bill: Background, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 400/10)
    - Steelhead Bill: Background, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/1)
    - Steelhead Bill: Hearing, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/2)
    - Steelhead Bill: Implementing Legislation, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/3)
    - Steelhead Bill: Press, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/4)
    - Steelhead Bill: Treaty/Annexes, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/5)
    - Timber: Contract Relief, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/6)
    - Timber: Implementation of Timber Relief, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/7)
    - Timber: Timber Relief Bill H.R. 2838, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/8)
    - Timber: Privatization, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 401/9)
    - Wilderness Act: Boulder River, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/1)
    - Wilderness Act: Constituent Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/2)
    - Wilderness Act: Glacier Peak, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/3)
    - Wilderness Act: Hydroelectric, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/4)
    - Wilderness Act: Interoffice Memos, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/5)
    - Wilderness Act: Mt. Baker, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/6)
    - Wilderness Act: Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/7)
    - Wilderness Act: Olympic National Forest, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/8)
    - Wilderness Act: Senate Legislation, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/9)
    - Wilderness Act: Timber, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 402/10)
    - Wilderness Areas, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 402/11)
    - Wilderness Road Area Review and Evaluation, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 403/1)
    - Wolf Project, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 403/2)
    - Wood Shares and Shingles, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 403/3)
  - Scott Cooper, 1977-1991; Subseries 2
    Note: Includes projects generally relate to telecommunications but also include some industry and trade; transportation; and finance.
    - Amtrack Reauthorization, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 404/1)
    - Auto-"Fair Practices in Automotive Products Act", 1981-1992 (Box-folder 404/2)
    - Boat Tax, 1990 (Box-folder 404/3)
    - Campaign Advertising Act, 1990 (Box-folder 404/4)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 404/5)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 405/1)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 405/2)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 405/3)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 405/4)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 406/1)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 406/2)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 406/3)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 406/4)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 407/1)
    - Conrail Sale, 1985 (Box-folder 407/2)
    - Credit Unions, 1990 (Box-folder 407/3)
    - Customs, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 407/4)
    - Customs: Blaine, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 407/5)
    - Customs: Blaine, WA, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 407/6)
    - Customs: Blaine, WA, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 407/7)
    - Customs: Blaine, WA, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 408/1)
    - Customs: Blaine and Point Roberts, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 408/2)
    - Customs: Canadian Red Raspberry Dumping, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 408/3)
    - Customs: Consolidation with Immigration and Naturalization, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 408/4)
    - Customs: Joint Customs and Immigration, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 408/5)
    - Customs: Lynden, WA, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 408/6)
    - Customs: Point Roberts, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 408/7)
    - Dilemmas of Party Leadership, 1985 (Box-folder 408/8)
    - Direct Foreign Investment: Bryant Amendment, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 409/1)
    - Direct Foreign Investment: Bryant Amendment, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 409/2)
    - Direct Foreign Investment: Compiled Statistics, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 409/3)
    - Direct Foreign Investment: Tracking, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 409/4)
    - Early Retirement Bill (INS, IRS, & Customs), 1982-1991 (Box-folder 409/5)
    - Early Retirement Bill (INS, IRS, & Customs), 1982-1991 (Box-folder 409/6)
    - Early Retirement Bill (INS, IRS, & Customs), 1982-1991 (Box-folder 409/7)
    - Early Retirement Bill (INS, IRS, & Customs), 1982-1991 (Box-folder 409/8)
    - Early Retirement Bill (INS, IRS, & Customs), 1982-1991 (Box-folder 409/9)
    - Earthquake Retirement Bill, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 410/1)
    - Earthquake Retirement Bill, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 410/2)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 410/3)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 410/4)
    - Goodwill Games, 1990 (Box-folder 410/5)
    - Industrial Policy, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 410/6)
    - Industrial Policy, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 411/1)
    - Industrial Policy Act, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 411/2)
    - Industrial Policy: Capital Formation, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 411/3)
    - Industrial Policy: Industrial Competitiveness Act, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 411/4)
    - Industrial Policy: National Industrial Strategy Act, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 412/1)
    - Insurance
      - Comptroller General's Report on State Regulation, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 412/2)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 412/3)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 412/4)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 413/1)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 413/2)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 413/3)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 413/4)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 414/1)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 414/2)
      - Fair Insurance Between Sexes, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 414/3)
      - Life Insurance Cost Disclosure, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 414/4)
      - Nondiscrimination in Insurance Act of 1983, Hearings, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 415/1)
      - Product Liability Crisis, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 415/2)
      - Unisex Insurance - National Press, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 415/3)
    - Securities
      - Securities, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 415/4)
      - American Stock Exchange - Surveillance Reports, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 415/5)
      - Briefing Book H.R.2032, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 415/6)
      - Briefing Book H.R. 2032, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 416/1)
      - Chicago Board of Trade & Chicago Mercantile Exchange "Computerized Trade Reconstruction Proposal", 1977-1985 (Box-folder 416/2)
      - E.S.M Government Securities, Inc., 1977-1985 (Box-folder 416/3)
      - E.S.M Government Securities, Inc. Background, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 416/4)
      - E.S.M Government Securities, Inc. Background, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 416/5)
      - E.S.M Government Securities, Inc., 1977-1985 (Box-folder 416/6)
      - E.S.M Government Securities, Inc. Working Documents, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 417/1)
      - Financial Fraud Detection and Disclosure Act, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 417/2)
      - Financial Planning, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 417/3)
      - Hearing on H.R. 2032 - A Bill to Amend the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 417/4)
      - Hearings on Insider Trading, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 417/5)
      - Hearings on the Public Securities Act of 1985, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 417/6)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 418/1)
      - Public Securities Act of 1985, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 418/2)
      - Public Securities Act of 1985, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 418/3)
      - "The Registry of Financial Planning Practitioners" Directory, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 418/4)
      - "Regulation of Financial Planners in the 1980's", Ralph C. Ferrara - Chairman, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 418/5)
      - Report on the High Yield Bonds (Junk Bonds), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 418/6)
      - "Summary of Key Policy Decisions", Security Industry Association, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 418/7)
    - Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance: Insider Trading Bill, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 418/8)
    - Subcommittee on Telecommunications and Finance: Insider Trading Bill, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 418/9)
    - Tax Reform, 1989 (Box-folder 419/1)
    - Telecommunications
      - Broadcast, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 419/2)
      - Broadcast, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 419/3)
      - Broadcast, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 419/4)
      - Broadcast, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 419/5)
      - Cable, 1990 (Box-folder 419/5)
      - Cable, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 420/1)
      - Cable, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 420/2)
      - Cable, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 420/3)
      - Cable, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 420/4)
      - Cable, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 420/5)
      - Cable, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 420/6)
      - Cable, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 421/1)
      - Cellular Telephones, 1990 (Box-folder 421/2)
      - Children's Television Practices Act, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 421/3)
      - Closed Captioning, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 421/4)
      - Communications Sattelite Coporation, 1990 (Box-folder 421/5)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 421/6)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1988 (Box-folder 422/1)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1988 (Box-folder 422/2)
      - Digital Audio Tapes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 422/3)
      - Digital Audio Tapes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 422/4)
      - Draft Proposal from Public Broadcasters to Independent Producers, 1988 (Box-folder 422/5)
      - Economic Concentration in the Communication Industry, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 423/1)
      - Federal Communications Committee, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 423/2)
      - Federal Communications Committee, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 423/3)
      - Federal Communications Committee, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 423/4)
      - Federal Communications Committee, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 423/5)
      - Fox Network Public Price Tier, 1990 (Box-folder 423/6)
      - High Definition Television, 1988 (Box-folder 423/7)
      - High Definition Television, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 424/1)
      - High Definition Television, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 424/2)
      - House Current Resolution 339, 1988 (Box-folder 424/3)
      - House Resolution 2828, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 424/4)
      - House Resolution 2828, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 424/5)
      - House Resolution 2828, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 424/6)
      - "Meritorious" Programming, 1990 (Box-folder 424/7)
      - Modified Final Judgement
        - "800" Access Services, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 424/8)
        - Alarm Industry, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 424/9)
        - Amendment to H.R.2140 by Swift, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 424/10)
        - American Newspaper Publishers Association (ANPA), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 424/11)
        - American Newspaper Publishers Association (ANPA), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/1)
        - American Newspaper Publishers Association (ANPA), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/2)
        - American Newspaper Publishers Association (ANPA) II, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/3)
        - Appellate Court, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/4)
        - AT& T, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/5)
        - Frank Blethes, American Newspaper Publishers Association, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/6)
        - Background, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/7)
        - Boeing, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/8)
        - Bypass, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/9)
        - Citizens for a Sound Economy, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/10)
        - Communication Workers of America (CWA), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 425/11)
        - Consumer Groups, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/1)
        - Cost Allocations, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/2)
        - Customer Proprietary Network Information, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/3)
        - Electronic Gateways, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/4)
        - Employee Protection, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/5)
        - Enhance Services, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/6)
        - Dingell, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/7)
        - Hearings, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/8)
        - Independent Yellow Pages, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/9)
        - Interexchange, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/10)
        - Judge Green, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 426/11)
        - Manufacturing, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/1)
        - Markey, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/2)
        - Markey Draft, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/3)
        - Markey's Strategy, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/4)
        - McCaw, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/5)
        - Ninth Circuit Appeals Court, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/6)
        - NYNEX, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/7)
        - Open Network Architecture (ONA), 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/8)
        - Positions, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/9)
        - Press, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 427/10)
        - Previous Drafts, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/1)
        - Rural Telephone Coalition (RTC), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/2)
        - Safeguards, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/3)
        - Statement of Principles, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/4)
        - State Regulators, National Association of RegulatoryUtility Commissioners (NARUC), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/5)
        - Strategy, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/6)
        - Tariffs 15 and 12, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/7)
        - Yellow Pages, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/8)
        - Modification of Final Judgement, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 428/9)
        - Background, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 429/1)
        - Background, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 429/2)
        - Rural Telecommunication Coalition, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 429/3)
      - Radio - National Association of Broadcasting Code, 1989 (Box-folder 429/4)
      - Radio - KAPS Mt. Vernon, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 429/5)
      - Radio - KGMI Bellingham, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 429/6)
      - Radio - KSER Everett, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 429/7)
      - Radio - KZAZ Bellingham, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 429/8)
      - Radio - KNTR Ferndale, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 430/1)
      - Radio - KNTR Ferndale, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 430/2)
      - Radio - Oak Harbor, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 430/3)
      - Rural Telephone Coalition, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 430/4)
      - Sale Price Disclosure, 1990 (Box-folder 430/5)
      - Satellite Homeviewer Copyright Act, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 430/6)
      - Satellite Scrambling - Hearing Before Subcommittee on and Finance, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 430/7)
      - Satellite Scrambling - Hearing Before Subcommittee on and Finance, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 430/8)
      - Satellite Scrambling, 1988 (Box-folder 431/1)
      - Satellite Television Fair Marketing Act, 1988 (Box-folder 431/2)
      - Specialized Mobile Radio Service, 1990 (Box-folder 431/3)
      - Swift's Broadcasting Bill, 1987 (Box-folder 431/4)
      - Tauzin/Satellite Viewer's Rights Act of 1990, circa 1990 (Box-folder 431/5)
      - Telecommunications and Trade with Japan, 1989 (Box-folder 431/6)
      - Television - Fisher Broadcasting, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 431/7)
      - Television - KCTS Seattle, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 431/8)
      - Television - KING & KOMO Seattle, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 431/9)
      - TV Marti, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 431/10)
      - TV Marti (Cuba), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 431/11)
      - TV Marti (Cuba), 1988-1990 (Box-folder 431/12)
      - TV Marti (Cuba), 1990 (Box-folder 432/1)
      - US West Business Averaging, 1988 (Box-folder 432/2)
    - Trade
      - Canadian Relations - Plywood, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 432/3)
      - Canadian Relations - US/Canada FTA, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 432/4)
      - European Relations, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 432/5)
      - The Environment and GATT, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 432/6)
      - Export Survey, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 432/7)
      - Export Survey - Results, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 432/8)
      - Export Survey - Results, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 432/9)
      - Exports - Federal Assistance, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/1)
      - Federal Trade Commission - General Motors, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/2)
      - Foreign Trade Zones, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/3)
      - Foreign Trade Zones, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/4)
      - Foreign Trade Zones, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/5)
      - Foreign Trade Zones, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/6)
      - Foreign Trade Zones - Gray's Harbor Application, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/7)
      - Foreign Trade Zones - Packet, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/8)
      - Foreign Trade Zones - Washington State, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 433/9)
      - FSX Deal with Japan, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 434/1)
      - House Resolution 371 - Unfair Trade Practices - GATT, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 434/2)
      - Japanese Relations, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 434/3)
      - Local Responses, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 434/4)
      - Timber to Japan, 1982 (Box-folder 434/5)
  - Scott Cooper and Drew Pettus, 1984-1985; Subseries 3
    Note: Includes projects related to Navy homeport issues including the status of the Everett Homeport.
    - Everett Homeport, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 435/1)
    - Everett Homeport, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 435/2)
    - Everett Homeport, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 435/3)
    - Everett Homeport, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 435/4)
    - Everett Homeport, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 435/5)
    - Everett Homeport, 1985 (Box-folder 436/1)
    - Everett Homeport, 1985 (Box-folder 436/2)
    - Navy Basing, 1984 (Box-folder 436/3)
    - Navy Basing, 1984 (Box-folder 436/4)
    - Navy Homeport Issues, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 436/5)
    - Navy Homeport Issues, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 436/6)
    - Navy Homeport Issues, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 436/7)
    - Navy Homeport Issues, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 437/1)
    - Navy Homeport Issues, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 437/2)
  - Mike Gillette, 1965-1990; Subseries 4
    Note: Includes projects related to the Bonneville Power Administration and other energy issues; the Clean Air Act; forestry issues including the spotted owl controversy; and hazardous waste.
    - Bonneville Power Administration
      - Administration, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 438/1)
      - Administration, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 438/2)
      - Billing Credits, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 438/3)
      - Billing Credits, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 438/4)
      - Billing Credits, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 438/5)
      - Conservation, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 438/6)
      - Conservation, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 438/7)
      - Conservation, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 439/1)
      - Conservation, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 439/2)
      - Conservation, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 439/3)
      - Conservation, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 439/4)
      - De-federalization, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 439/5)
      - De-federalization, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 439/6)
      - De-federalization, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 439/7)
      - De-federalization, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 439/8)
      - De-federalization, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 439/9)
      - De-federalization, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 440/1)
      - De-federalization, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 440/2)
      - De-federalization, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 440/3)
      - De-federalization, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 440/4)
      - De-federalization, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 440/5)
      - De-federalization, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 440/6)
      - De-federalization, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 440/7)
      - Industrial/Commercial Conservation, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 440/8)
      - Model Conservation Standards, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 441/1)
      - Model Conservation Standards, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 441/2)
      - Pease User Fee, 1985 (Box-folder 441/3)
      - Petri Amendment to 1985 Omnibus Water Bill, 1985 (Box-folder 441/4)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/5)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/6)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/7)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/8)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/9)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/10)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/11)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/12)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/13)
      - Rates, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 441/14)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/1)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/2)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/3)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/4)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/5)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/6)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/7)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/8)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/9)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/10)
      - Rates, 1987 (Box-folder 442/11)
      - Repayment - Amortization Period, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/1)
      - Repayment - Congressional Research Requests, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/2)
      - Repayment - G.A.O. Reports, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/3)
      - Repayment - Grace Commission, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/4)
      - Repayment - Interest Rates, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/5)
      - Repayment - Legal Background, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/6)
      - Repayment Practices - Background, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/7)
      - Repayment Reform - Administration FY 86 Budget Proposal, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/8)
      - Repayment Reform - Metzenbaum Bill (S.2788), 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/9)
      - Repayment Study Method, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 443/10)
      - Straight-Line Payments, 1966 (Box-folder 443/11)
      - Senate Budget Committee Proposal: FY 88, 1987 (Box-folder 443/12)
      - Washington Public Power Supply System
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 1 & 3 - Luce Legal Exhibits, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 443/13)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 1 & 3 - Amendment # 317 - Construction Costs, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 444/1)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 1 & 3 - Assignment of Debt, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 444/2)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 1 & 3 - Billing Utilities, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 444/3)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 1 & 3 - Rep. Weaver Hearing, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 444/4)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Bankruptcy Option, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 444/5)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Background Info. (A), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 444/6)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Background Info. (B), 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/1)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Debt Reduction Option, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/2)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Default Analyses, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/3)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Default Analyses, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/4)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Default Options, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/5)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - Dispute Resolution Court, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/6)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - H.R.3152 Bailout, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/7)
        - Bond Debt Default - NP 4 & 5 - H.R.4077 Tax Exempt, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 445/8)